factoryrush.com 2014-06-25

# Factory Rush - Our Policies

At Factory Rush, we endeavor to provide you the best shopping experience at every step. We take an extra care to ensure that your order reaches you safe, intact and timely.

For all the subsequent purchases of Rs. 1000 or more, we will deliver the order to your doorstep Free of cost. A shipping charge of Rs. 59 will be applicable to all orders under Rs. 1000. 

Our goal is to deliver the product within 5-7 working days, if you live in metros. It could extend to 8-10 working days from the day the order is placed with us depending on the where it is supposed to deliver. However, there might be circumstances beyond our control where this timeline cannot be maintained. In such cases, we ensure that the product reaches you within 12-15 days of purchase.

We avail the services of the most reliable and leading logistic companies like Delhivery, Fedex and Bluedart to ensure safe and timely delivery of your order(s). You can track the order status after placing it. The delivery status will indicate following responses:

* On-hold: Your order is not confirmed (In case of COD orders)
* Processing: Your order is getting packed for delivery
* Shipped: Your order has been dispatched from our warehouse and is with the logistics partner for delivery
* Delivered: Your order has been delivered to you

All of your orders will be dispatched within 24 hours of placement. Working days excludes Sunday and Public holidays.

We will keep you informed on the status of your order including delays if any. In case of non-delivery of any item in your order, you will not be billed for the same, and/or the you will receive the full store credits/ refund equivalent to the amount of the same product.

**Product Availability**

We make an earnest effort to make sure that product listed on our website is available in stock and that the prices shown are correct. In the unlikely event when we’re not able to send your order or replacement due to unavailability of the product in our warehouse, we will inform you within a maximum of 2 working days from the date you place the order. 

While we stand behind the high quality and design of our products, we stand by you, too. If you are dissatisfied for any reason, our replacement process is simple offering an easy 15 days replacement policy for you. You can conveniently return any product and avail another product from our site.

Products returned for replacement must be unused and should have original packaging and tags that they are shipped with. The product would be acceptable only if:

* The product delivered was damaged
* The product delivered was not as described at the time of purchase
* The product ordered does not fit to size

Kindly follow the below mentioned steps to send the replacement products back to Factory Rush:

* Place the item in its original packaging
* Mention your order number on a paper or attach the original invoice
* Seal the package properly
* Use reliable courier service for any return
* Scan and send the courier receipt for reimbursement of courier charges

Please ship back the product(s) to our registered office address mentioned below:

Factory Rush Retail  
Plot No – 319 , Village Barthal,  
Sector 26, Dwarka  
New Delhi-110075‎

We recommend you to use reliable courier service to ship back the product. Factory Rush will not be responsible for any loss or damage to the good(s) during transit. If products are lost or damaged in transit, it would result to billing or non-refund of the amount equivalent to the loss or damage. The return will be closed within 15 days from the day we receive the item(s) to be returned from the customer. However for top cities, we provide reverse pick-up services but the shipping charges in this case would be bear by customer only.

Once your return is received by us, a quality check will be performed on the returned items by our quality team. This is subject to your return having met the requirements of being unused and unwashed.

Any returned product received by us that do not meet the above mentioned conditions, the product will not be accepted and will be returned back to you at your expense. No amount will be reimbursed in this case.

**Exchanges**

We would love to exchange your product for a new colour and/or size or another product but please make sure that the new product requested during exchange should have equivalent or higher amount than the returned product.

**Cancellations**

We will be able to accept order change or cancellation requests any time before we ship your order. Unfortunately, we cannot cancel orders once the shipment is out from our warehouse for delivery.

Our goal is to make your return and exchanges experience as comfortable as possible.

Use of the Website – By accessing the website, you warrant and represent to the website owner that you are legally entitled to do so and to make use of information made available via website.

1\. Trademarks – The trademarks, names, logos and service marks (collectively “trademarks”) displayed on this website are registered and unregistered trademarks of the website owner. Nothing contained on this website should be construed as granting any license or right to use any trademark without the prior permission of the website owner.

2\. External Links – External links may be provided for your convenience, but they are beyond the control of the website owner and no representation is made as to their content. Use or reliance on any external links and the content thereon provided is at your own risk.

3\. Warranties – The website owner makes no warranties, representations, statements or guarantees whether express, implied in law or residual regarding the website.

4\. Disclaimer of Liability – factoryrush.com will not be responsible or liable for any special, incidental, indirect or consequential damages of any kind in connection with this agreement, even if factoryrush.com has been informed in advance. In particular, the website owner shall not be responsible for and disclaims all liability for any loss, liability, damage whether direct, indirect or consequential or expense of any nature whatsoever which may be suffered by you as a result of or which may be attributable, directly or indirectly, to your access and use of the website.

5\. Conflict of Terms – If there is a conflict and/or contradiction between the provisions of the website terms and conditions and the other relevant terms and conditions, policies which relate specifically to a particular section of the website shall prevail in respect of your use of the relevant section of the website.

6\. Severability – Any provision of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices, which is or becomes unenforceable in any jurisdiction, whether due to being void, invalidity, illegality, unlawfulness or for any reason, shall be treated as void and the remaining provisions of any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices shall remain in full force and effect.

7\. Applicable Laws – This agreement shall be governed by and interpreted and construed in accordance with the laws of India. The place of jurisdiction shall be in New Delhi. The parties agree that the courts located in India shall have exclusive jurisdiction over all controversies arising under this agreement and agree that venue is proper in those courts.

We value the trust you hold in Factory Rush. Please read the following privacy policy carefully. While using and/or accessing our website we acknowledge that you read, understand and agree to be bound to all the terms mentioned in this privacy policy and other pages of this website.

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without/with notice. The revised privacy policy is effective immediately when posted on the website. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this privacy policy periodically for your reference.

**1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information Name, Email Address and Phone Number from you when you set up or connect an account with Factory Rush We do use your contact information to send you promotional and/or timely offers.

**2\. Use of Demographic and Profile Data**  
We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. Your information is also used to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online offers, products, services and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. In our efforts to continuously improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users’ activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

**3\. Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Factory Rush places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer’s hard drive. Factory Rush cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven’t changed your computer’s settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies or disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

**4\. Sharing of Personal Information**  
We may share personal information with other corporate entities and affiliates to help, detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts. These entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders, or other legal process. Factory Rush will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity.

**5\. Security Precautions**  
Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**6\. Advertising**  
We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, email address or any personally identifying information about the user.
